They aimed to build the ultimate fighting machine... they missed.
The Pentagon Wars is a comedy, drama, war film directed by Richard Benjamin.
From the director of “Made In America” and “The Money Pit” comes a hilarious
look at one of the most expensive blunders in military history.
Over 17 years and almost as many billion dollars have gone into
devising the BFV (Bradley Fighting Vehicle).
There's only one problem.
it doesn't work.
(Spoiler alert: 25 years later ...
it does work.)
General Partridge, played by Kelsey Grammer.
Colonel James Burton, played by Cary Elwes.
Sgt. Fanning, played by Viola Davis.
Colonel J.D. Bock, played by John C. McGinley.
Major William Sayers, played by Tom Wright.
Sgt. Benjamn Dalton, played by Clifton Powell.
The Pentagon Wars is a 1998 HBO comedy film directed by Richard Benjamin based on The Pentagon Wars: Reformers
Challenge the Old Guard, a book written by retired United States Air Force Colonel James G.
Burton about the development of the Bradley Fighting Vehicle.
The film explores themes of vietnam war, gulf war, army, pentagon, dark comedy.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and emotional.